Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Submission to the Advisory Planning Committee on Medical Care, 1960; Publication (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Submission to the Aged and Long Term Illness Survey Committee, 1962; Publication (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Submission Committee of Review of the Workmen's Compensation (Accident Fund) Act, 1963; Publication (Box 126, Folder 2)
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Legislative submission Government of the Province of Saskatchewan, 1964; Publication (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Legislative submission Government of the Province of Saskatchewan, 1965; Publication (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Submission to the CLC Commission on Constitution & Structure., 1966; Publication (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Submission to the Joint (Govt.-Univ.) Committee on Higher Ed., 1966; Publication (Box 126, Folder 3)
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A case for employment in Saskatchewan, 1961; Publication (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The case for a 40 hour, five day work week law in Saskatchewan, 1961; Publication (Box 126, Folder 4)
- Seafarers' International Union of Canada., Publication (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Seafarers International Union of Canada relative to the Report of the Industrial Inquiry Commission on the Disruption of Shipping, 1963; Publication (Box 126, Folder 5)
    Author: Seafarers' International Union of Canada.
- Canadian Unions, Publication (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Canadian Unions meet on merger, 1956; Publication (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Quebec Unionists see merger need, 1956; Publication (Box 126, Folder 6)
- Trades and Labor Congress of Canada, Publication (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Union label directory, 1950; Publication (Box 126, Folder 7)
    Author: Trades and Labor Congress of Canada
- Trades and Labor Congress of Canada, Publication (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: An historical review, the Trades and labor congress of Canada, 1873-1950, Publication (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Convention call, 1937; Publication (Box 126, Folder 8)
- Canadian Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Paying the shot for what?, Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Pourquoi payer vos dus?, Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
    Language: French.
  - Item 3: Citizen trade unionist ..., 1945; Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
    Author: Idele Louise Wilson
  - Item 4: Le Diplomate du travailleur, Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The worker's diplomat, Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Workers' Educational Association, Research bulletin - No. 16, Publication (Box 126, Folder 9)
    Author: Canadian Federation of Labor